

I'm a 29 years old Web Developer from Turkey based in Antalya. I love everything that has to do with HTML, CSS, JavasScript, Node.js, React, SASS, Less, Preprocessors like Gulp, Webpack and I everything new around the Web.

OBJECTIVES

A developer with 6 years open-source experience. Worked on cutting edge applications mobile and web platforms as an outsourcing partner to web design agencies. Expert level in front-end development technologies, responsive design and UI performance. Having back-end and user interface design experience. Learning the Dart lang. and I keen to develop mobile applications with the Flutter framework.

EDUCATION

2008-2012

Art Education - Bachelor's Degree Pamukkale State University - Denizli, TR.

2014-2017

Educational Technologies - Non-thesis Master's Degree Suleyman Demirel State University - ISPARTA, TR.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS and CSS preprocessors such as SASS, SCSS and LESS	
JavaScript and related libraries like ReactJS, Electron	
CSS frameworks like Bootstrap, Foundation	
JavaScript front-end workflow tooling with Gulp, Grunt, WebPack	
Knowledge of MVC back-end frameworks, JSON and REST APIs	
Significant experience in building mobile responsive & adaptive applications	
Mobile-first design & progressive web applications	
Experience in user interface design and back-end development	
Websockets and realtime communication at the UI	
Git Version Control System	

SELECTED WORKS

KeepWords.

A simple tool for adding the new words which you just learned. Tech stack: Firebase, PreactJS, Sass. It's a progressive web application (PWA) and it comes with offline sync built-in.

keepwords-com.firebaseapp.com

Fupio.

A simple microblogging app based on a blockchain and blockstack. github.com/fupio

Huhu

An experimental script language for kids, written in Python. github.com/mehmetkose/huhu

Boilerplate.

Boilerplate project for creating hybrid web applications. It's backed by PreactJS, Electron & Cordova. Uses SASS for styling. github.com/mehmetkose/boilerplate

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2019 -

Mobirolle

Front End Developer in Antalya, TR

It's a product company. Mostly I'm building PWA's for the company. Re-building the old UI's, by using ReactJS, Redux and related technologies.

July 2017 - 2017 Jun

Freelancing on Upwork

Hybrid Application Developer / Remote

I've done couple projects on Upwork. I wrote a technical paper for Pusher about websockets. Another project that I worked was a food finder app. Built a PWA by using React and Cordova on Firehase

Feb 2016 - Jun 2017

Ertisya Software

Full Stack Web Developer in Isparta, TR

Created some Odoo (an open source ERP) modules for this company. Added some features for a Diango project. Created a microservice for video convertion.

Nov 2015 - Feb 2016

Ihya Web Tech

Full Stack Web Developer in Denizli, TR

I've created lots of end-user website with PHP & Python backend. Created some sharp web crawlers to collapse some data. Experienced how Google Crawlers works and coding for SEO.

Mar 2013 - Jun 2014

ReachPod Social Media Tool & Media Agency

Full Stack Web Developer in Istanbul, TR

Worked with a 2 great senior developer at this startup. Kept working with Django Framework and I've done some UI parts of the product.

Feb 2012 - Sep2013

Butigo Social Media Tool & Media Agency

Junior Backend Developer in Istanbul, TR

I worked as a junior python programmer and I've experienced working with a real team, and building a Django application.

Nov 2009 - Oct 2010

Technoone

Intern - in Denizli, TR

At this period I had a change to apply what I learned and show up my skills. Usually worked with XHTML and web Ul's.

HABBITS AND INTEREST







TAGS

#Javascript #es6 #node #html #css #sass #scss #react #preactJS #firebase #electron #python #nginx #mongodb #rethinkdb #flutter